Sanctuary Movement Trial papers, 1979-1992
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 11: Appeals, 1981-1989
  - Subseries 2: Legal Briefs, ca 1980's
    - Briefs--Appellants' Opening Part One (Part 2), 1987 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Briefs--Appellants' Opening Part One (Part 3), 1987 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Briefs--Appellants' Opening Part Two, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Briefs--Appellants’ Petition for Rehearing and Suggestions for Rehearing En Banc, ca 1980's (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Briefs--Appellants’ Reply, ca 1980's (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Briefs--Appellants’ Reply Part Two, ca 1980's (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Briefs--Appellee’s Response to Appellants’ Petition for Rehearing and Suggestion En Banc, ca 1980's (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Briefs-- Brief of Appellants--Draft (Part 1), 1987 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Briefs-- Brief of Appellants --Draft (Part 2), 1987 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Briefs--Brief of Appellee (Part 1), 1988 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Briefs--Brief of Appellee (Part 2), 1988 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Briefs--Brief of Appellee (Part 3), 1988 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Briefs--Brief of the Institute for Youth Advocacy, the St. Anthony Foundation, the National Lawyers Guild, Travelers and Immigrants Aid and Centro Presente as Amici Curiae in Support of Defendant Reverend Anthony Clark, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Briefs-- Government’s Supplemental Excerpt of Record, Volume I, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Briefs-- Government’s Supplemental Excerpt of Record, Volume II, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Briefs-- Government’s Supplemental Excerpt of Record, Volume III (Part 1), ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Briefs-- Government’s Supplemental Excerpt of Record, Volume III (Part 2), ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Briefs--Older Relevant Court Case Briefs for Research, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 1: Assorted Background and Appeal Materials, ca 1980's
    - File #1--1980 Refugee Act, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - File #2--Amend Conditions of Release, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - File #3--Amicus Curiae Suppression of Evidence, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - File #4--Arizona Sanctuary Defense Fund, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - File #5--Assorted Motions (1), ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - File #6--Assorted Motions (2), ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - File #7--Assorted Government Responses (1), ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - File #8--Assorted Government Responses (2), ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - File #9--Assorted Government Responses--Supplemental, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - File #10--Being Held in Contempt, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - File #11--Change of Address, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - File #12--Change of Venue, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - File #13--Disclosure of Grand Jury Transcripts and Production of Testimony, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - File #14--Disclosure of the Identities of Informants, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - File #15--Dismissal of Indictment, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - File #16--Duplicity, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - File #17--Equal Protection, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - File #18--Extension of Time, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - File #19--F.R.Crim.P. Motion, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - File #20--Fair Trial Directive, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - File #21--Free Exercise of Religion Issues, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - File #22--Futility and Duress, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - File #23--Government’s Disclosure of Witnesses, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - File #24--Government’s Motion per 18 U.S.C 6003(a), ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - File #25--Hearings, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - File #26--Infiltration, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - File #27--International Law, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - File #28--Intra-District Transfer, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - File #29--Issues Relevant to Intent and Excluding Evidence of Intent, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - File #30--Jesus Cruz, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - File #31--Joinder One, ca 1980's (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - File #32--Joinder Two, ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - File #33--Motion for Discovery One, ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - File #34--Motion for Discovery Two, ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - File #35--Motion in Limine (Part 1), ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - File #36--Motion in Limine (Part 2), ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - File #37--Motion in Limine (Part 3), ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - File #38--Motion to Suppress Documents Seized from Residence, ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - File #39--Multiplicity, ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - File #40--Preclude Identification Testimony, ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - File #41--Rehearing En Banc, ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - File #42--Religious Based Arguments, ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - File #43--Require Elections and Dismissal of Multiplicitous Counts, ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - File #44--Rule 89, ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - File #45--San Francisco Calendar, ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - File #46--Stipulations, ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - File #47--Unwarranted Infringement on Right to Freedom of Religion, ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - File #48--Voir Dire, ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - File #49--Witness Lists, ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 3: Motions and Government Responses, ca 1980's
    - Peggy Hutchinson--Appeal Law File (Part 1), ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Peggy Hutchinson --Appeal Law File (Part 2), ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Peggy Hutchinson--Attorney Notebook (Part 1), ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Peggy Hutchinson--Attorney Notebook (Part 2), ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Peggy Hutchinson --Authority to Pay Court Appointed Counsel File, 1989-1990 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Peggy Hutchinson --Correspondence File, 1985-1989 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Peggy Hutchinson --Motion to Terminate Probation, 1987-1988 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Peggy Hutchinson --Orders File, ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Peggy Hutchinson --Pleadings File One (Part 1), ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Peggy Hutchinson --Pleadings File One (Part 2), ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Peggy Hutchinson --Pleadings File Two, ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Peggy Hutchinson --Sentencing File, ca 1980's (Box 43, Folder 30)
- Series XII: Background/Pretrial Material, 1981-1991
  - Subseries 1: Assorted Background/Pretrial Materials, ca 1980's
    - Background--Attorney Notes--Jesus Cruz Testimony, ca 1980's (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Central American Refugee Information Center, 1982-1983 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Background--Controlled Load, ca 1980's (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Background--Gag Order Materials, ca 1980's (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Background--Juror Summaries, ca 1980's (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Background-- Mock Trial, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Background--Newsletter--Codefam, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Background--Notes for the Defense--Closing Arguments (Part 1), ca 1980's (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Background-- Notes for the Defense--Closing Arguments (Part 2), ca 1980's (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Background--Salvadoran Refugee Network, ca 1980's (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Background--Sanctuary Venue Survey, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Background--Telephone Notebooks, ca 1980's (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Background--Trial Exhibits--Court, ca 1980's (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Background--Trial Exhibits--Defendants, ca 1980's (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Background--The Valley Religious Task Force on Central America, ca 1980's (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Background--Statements from the Whitehouse, Senator Wilson, and Lord Avebury, ca 1980's (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Background--List of Television Coverage, ca 1980's (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 2: Background--Guatemala, ca 1980's
    - Guatemala--Bulletins--Enfoprensa: Information on Guatemala, 1984, 1987-1991 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Guatemala--Bulletins--Guatemala: News in Brief, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Guatemala--Bulletins--Guatemala Solidarity Committee (GUASO)--Guatemala Update, 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Guatemala--Bulletins--Inter-Hemispheric Education Resource Center, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Guatemala--Bulletins--Noticias de Guatemala, 1988-1990 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Guatemala--Comisión de Derechos Humanos de Guatemala (1), 1984, 1987-1988 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Guatemala--Comisión de Derechos Humanos de Guatemala (2), 1988-1989 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Guatemala--Guatemalan Bishops’ Conference--The Cry for Land: Joint Pastoral Letter, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Guatemala--Health Care, 1987-1988 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Guatemala--Newsletters--Archbishop of Guatemala--Clamor, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Guatemala--Newsletters--Ceri~Gua, 1988-1990 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Guatemala--Newsletters--Diócesis de San Cristóbal--Caminante, 1984-1985 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Guatemala--Newsletters--Grupo de Apoyo Mutuo, 1986-1989, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Guatemala--Newsletters--Guatemalan Church in Exile, , 1986-1987 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Guatemala-- Newspaper and Magazine Articles, 1983, 1987-1989 (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Guatemala--NISGUA (Network in Solidarity with the People of Guatemala), 1988-1991 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - Guatemala--Periodicals-- Secretaria de Ayuda a Refugiados Guatemaltecos, 1989-1991 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Guatemala-- Pro Justice and Peace Committee of Guatemala, 1986-1991 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Guatemala--Travel Information and Brochures, no date (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Guatemala--Voices of Justice and Solidarity Membership Materials, circa 1980’s (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 3: Background--Related Cases (Texas), ca 1980's
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--“Anna”, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - GRelated Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Bourgouis, Philippe, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Clements, Charles, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Coatsworth, John, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Cozette, Gary L., 1984 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Cruz, Valeentin, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Duignan, Sister Maureen, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Forche, Carolyn, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Ford, William P., 1984 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Funes, Rudy, 19841 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Goldman, Robert Kogod, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--“Hector”, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Hoff, Anne M., 1984 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Leogrande, William M., 1984 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Mattison, Henry, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Mendez, Juan E., 1984 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Montgomery, Tommie Sue, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Neier, Aryeh, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Parker, Karen, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Ramirez, Secundino, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Rone, Jemera, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Savala, Epifanio Canales, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--Solorzano, Jesus, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Deposition--“Suzanne”, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Professional Paper--American Civil Liberties Union Fund--The Fates of Salvadorans Expelled from the U.S, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Testimony--Ramos, Pedro Antonio, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Trial Materials--Briefs, circa 1980’s (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Trial Materials--Index of Exhibits, circa 1980’s (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - Related Cases (Texas)--Trial Materials--Motions and Government Responses, circa 1980’s (Box 45, Folder 33)
- Series XIII: Individuals, 1981-1991
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Affidavit Materials, circa 1980’s (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Assorted Materials, circa 1980’s (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Attorney Handwritten Notes, no date (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Attorney Notebook, circa 1980’s (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Brady Materials File One, circa 1980’s (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Brady Materials File Two, circa 1980’s (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Certiorari Petition, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Correspondence File One, 1985-1986 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Correspondence File Two, 1985-1986 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Correspondence File Three, 1985-1986, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--INS--Reports and Memorandums, circa 1980’s (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Jury Instructions, circa 1980’s (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Memorandums, circa 1980’s (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Motion for Discovery, circa 1980’s (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Motion to Dismiss International Law File, circa 1980’s (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File One (Part 1), circa 1980’s (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File One (Part 2), circa 1980’s (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File Two (Part 1), circa 1980’s (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File Two (Part 2), circa 1980’s (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File Three (Part 1), circa 1980’s (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File Three (Part 2), circa 1980’s (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File Four (Part 1), circa 1980’s (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File Four (Part 2), circa 1980’s (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File Five (Part 1), circa 1980’s (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File Five (Part 2), circa 1980’s (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File Six (Part 1), circa 1980’s (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File Six (Part 2), circa 1980’s (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File Seven (Part 1), circa 1980’s (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - , Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File Seven (Part 2), circa 1980’s (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - , Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File Eight (Part 1), circa 1980’s (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - , Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File Eight (Part 2), circa 1980’s (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - , Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File Nine (Part 1), circa 1980’s (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - , Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File Nine (Part 2), circa 1980’s (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - , Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File Ten, circa 1980’s (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - , Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Pleading File--Orders, circa 1980’s (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - , Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Publicity File, circa 1980’s (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - , Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Sanctuary Burglaries, circa 1980’s (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - , Defendant--Hutchinson, Peggy--Supplemental Evidence in Support of Renewal of Motions, circa 1980’s (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - , Defendant--LeWin, Wendy—Overt Acts, circa 1980’s (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - , Defendant--LeWin, Wendy—Correspondence to, circa 1980’s (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - , Defendant--LeWin, Wendy—Alan Thurber (father), circa 1980’s (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Series XIV: Post-Trial Miscellaneous Material, 1982-1992
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1982-1986 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Appeals, 1987-1992 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Background and Miscellaneous Information 1 of 2, undated (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Background and Miscellaneous Information 2 of 2, undated (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Borders and Crossing--Research, circa 1980’s (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Borders and Crossing—June Edition, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Center for human Rights and Constitutional Law, 1989-1992 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Chile Solidarity Action, undated (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Coalition for Immigration Representation, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Deportation Cases, undated (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Ellen Yaroshefsky, circa 1985 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Fredy Armanda Rodas-Ortega, circa 1990 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Interreligious Foundation for Community Organization, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Junior High Students’ Writings, circa 1985 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Jury Notes, circa 1985 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Motions to Dismiss, 1985-1987 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters, Brochures, Pamphlets 1 of 2, undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, Brochures, Pamphlets 2 of 2, undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Official U.S. Circuit Court Material, circa 1985 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Pastors for Peace, circa 1985 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Probation information, circa 1985 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Religious Material, undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Related Legislative Information, undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Sanctuary Committee, circa 1985 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Sanctuary Defense Fund, Arizona—Trial Updates, circa 1985 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Sanctuary Defense Fund, National—General, Correspondence, Minutes, circa 1985 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Sanctuary Defense Fund, National—Media packet and Related Material, circa 1985 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Sanctuary Movement notebook, undated (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Support Letters, circa 1985 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Trial Materials, Miscellaneous, circa 1985 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Trial Notebook, circa 1985 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Tucson Ecumenical Council, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Unitarian Universalist Association Handbook, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Unitarian Universalist Association, circa 1985 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - United Universalist Service Committee, circa 1980 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Various Count Cases and Verdicts, circa 1990 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Valley Religious Task Force on Central America, circa 1990 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Salvadoran Election Monitor 1 of 2, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Salvadoran Election Monitor 2 of 2, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 27)
- Series XV: Newspaper Clippings 1979-1992
  - News Clippings, undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1974, 1979, 1981-1983 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, January-May 1985 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, June-July 1985 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, August-December 1985 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, January 1986 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, February 1986 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, March 1986 1 of 3 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, March 1986 2 of 3 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, March 1986 3 of 3 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, April 1986 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, May-December 1986 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, 1987, 1989, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 13)